

CONTACT

- 41 Bis Cours de Vincennes 75020 Paris, France.
- gabriel.pironneau@gmail.com
- in /in/gabriel-pironneau-7954b6171
- gabrielpironneau.com
- github.com/arkea-tech
- ₩ gitlab.com/arkea-tech

HOBBIES

Sport : 10 years of *tennis* in club and 3 years of *skateboarding* for leisure.

Music : Regular practice of *guitar* since 5 years.

Travel : Since my earliest childhood I have travelled to many countries, especially in *Asia* and *North America*.

LANGUAGES

French, native.
English, fluent.
Korean, Intermediate.

Gabriel PIRONNEAU

Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Developer in freelance, I'm passionate about web & mobile development as well as entrepreneurship.

I aim to acquire new skills in designing and developing innovative solutions.

SKILLS

Languages & tools:

- Javascript, Typescript, Wordpress, HTML/CSS, XML.
- Java, Kotlin, Python, C++, C.
- Go, Dart, Flutter, Swift, Ruby.

Technologies:

- Vue.js, React.js, React Native, Node.js, Angular.js.
- Express.js, Redux, Axios, Sequelize, Vite, Quasar, Git.
- Docker, MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Material UI.

EDUCATION

Epitech, graduate school and Master's degree of Digital Innovation and Computer Science - Feb 2018/Sept 2022.

One semester in Mathematics and Physics at Sorbonne University Pierre and Marie Curie - Sept 2017/ Jan 2018.

French Baccalaureate Diploma in Sciences - 2017.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CNRS, Jan 2023 - Feb 2023:

Part-time freelance as a Full Stack Web Developer in Vue.js/Node.js. Web application for energy consumption monitoring and awareness.

Capgemini France, April 2022 - Feb 2023:

Permanent position as a Full Stack Web Developer in React.js/Java. Plateform to analyse and manipulate graphs for the "Ministry of Armed Forces".

AFD Tech Paris, Sept 2021 - March 2022:

Part-time internship as a Full Stack Mobile Developer in React Native/Node.js. Mobile application for project and user management.